{
    "id": "a9806d0ad6fa4352ac28c460295d8bd3",
    "title": "Confusing Words Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Just because you are old doesn’t mean you have to be ……………………….",
            "description": "Idle means inactive or doing nothing.",
            "answers": [
                "idle",
                "idol",
                "idyll"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Hindus worship ………………………….",
            "description": "An idol is an image of a god.",
            "answers": [
                "idols",
                "idylls",
                "idles"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Our Caribbean holiday was a perfect ……………………………………",
            "description": "Idyll can mean a charmingly rustic life.",
            "answers": [
                "idyll",
                "idol",
                "idle"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The police are cracking down on ……………………………. gambling.",
            "description": "Illicit means not legal.",
            "answers": [
                "elicit",
                "illicit",
                "ilicit"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The investigator was able to ………………………………….. a confession from the accused.",
            "description": "To elicit is to draw out.",
            "answers": [
                "evict",
                "elicit",
                "illicit"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The ………………………………. of youth fade with maturity.",
            "description": "An illusion is a false belief.",
            "answers": [
                "allusions",
                "illusions",
                "elusions"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The ……………………………. state of tranquility soon erupted into war.",
            "description": "Illusory means unreal.",
            "answers": [
                "illusory",
                "allusory",
                "illusive"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "An ……………………………. set director can always enhance the play.",
            "description": "Imaginative means original, creative or inventive.",
            "answers": [
                "imaginary",
                "imaginative",
                "imaginational"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Lending someone your passport is an ……………………………. thing to do.",
            "description": "Both words mean foolish, dumb or stupid.",
            "answers": [
                "imbecilic",
                "idiotic",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The young men consumed an …………………………………. amount of wine and fell asleep.",
            "description": "Immoderate means excessive.",
            "answers": [
                "immodest",
                "immoderate",
                "immaculate"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The management and the trade union have reached an ……………………………",
            "description": "Impasse means deadlock or stalemate.",
            "answers": [
                "impasse",
                "passe",
                "impass"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The water shortage …………………………………….. the city’s fire-fighting capacity.",
            "description": "Impaired means crippled or damaged.",
            "answers": [
                "impaled",
                "impaired",
                "unpaired"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}